https://www.infertilityalabama.com/privacy-policy/

We apologize for the inconvenience, but your browser is currently not supported by this website.
Please try another browser, or install the latest version of your favorite browser below:
Filter by Categories
[:en]Fertilty 101[:]
[:en]IVF Procedure[:]
[:en]Research[:]
[:en]Wellness[:]
×
Our CenterCustomer Care Specialist CalendarWhy Choose CRMUpdate on Coronavirus (COVID-19)Military DiscountsMeet Our TeamFertility Center LocationsPatient TestimonialsIVF Success RatesOur PartnersJoin Our TeamContact UsUnderstanding FertilityWhen to See a Fertility SpecialistThe Typical Infertility Treatment JourneyThe Monthly Ovulation CycleInfertility in WomenInfertility in MenSingle ParenthoodDonors and SurrogacyLGBT Family PlanningGetting Pregnant After 35Natural Ways to Increase FertilityFertility GlossaryTreatment OptionsDiagnostic ProceduresSurgical ProceduresIntrauterine Insemination (IUI)In Vitro Fertilization (IVF) TreatmentEgg FreezingPreserving Fertility after Cancer and IllnessFertility Counseling and Support GroupsFinancial GuidanceWill My Insurance Cover Treatment?What Are Typical Treatment Costs?Financing OptionsMulti-Cycle Discount ProgramsFinancial Counseling and SupportFirst StepsRequest an AppointmentYour First VisitEmotional ConsiderationsLong-Distance PatientsFertility BlogTreatment Options
share
Request an Appointment
251-438-4200
Request Online
Related Content
Celebrating 25 Years of Excellence
Fertility Blog
Thank You For Your Payment
Terms & Conditions
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully. This Privacy Policy is subject to the Terms and Conditions posted on this Site and may be amended without notice. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy on this site. Site users are encouraged to periodically check this policy to see if any changes have been made that may affect them. By using the The Center for Reproductive Medicine site, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Personal-identifying information is data that can be used to identify or contact you The Center for Reproductive Medicine collects only the personal-identifying information you provide to us through webpages at infertilityalabama.com (the “Site”), such as when you request information about the The Center for Reproductive Medicine services, or when you use certain features of the Site, such as making an appointment or emailing general inquiries to the practice. All personal-identifying information, however collected, is used only by The Center for Reproductive Medicine and for the sole purpose of acting as requested by the user and responding to the user, and is not disclosed to any third parties. This Privacy Policy does not apply to any other data, including, without limitation, data that The Center for Reproductive Medicine may collect on websites that are linked to the Site.
The Center for Reproductive Medicine reserves the right to disclose any personal-identifying or nonpersonal-identifying information collected through the Site if we are required to do so by law or if we reasonably believe that such action is necessary in order to: fulfill a government request, conform with the requirements of the law or to comply with legal process served on us; protect against misuse or unauthorized use of the Site; transfer to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets or other corporate change respecting The Center for Reproductive Medicine or this Site; protect or defend the legal rights or property of The Center for Reproductive Medicine, this Site or its users; or, in an emergency, to protect the health and safety of this Site’s users or the general public.
We may also collect nonpersonal-identifying information through the use of “cookies”, which are small text files stored on your computer’s hard drive or web browser and are used to aid in webpage navigation. The Center for Reproductive Medicine does not store any personal-identifying information in any cookies on your computer. Site users have the option whether or not to accept cookies by resetting their web browsers to give notice when a cookie is being sent to their hard drive. Cookies may also be deleted from a hard drive, however, some parts of this Site may not function properly or may be slowed considerably if cookies are not accepted or disabled.
The Center for Reproductive Medicine uses Google Analytics as its web analytics tool. It helps us understand how visitors engage with our website. As a Google Analytics customers The Center for Reproductive Medicine can view a variety of reports about how visitors interact with our website so we can improve the user experience. Google Analytics collects information anonymously. It reports website trends without identifying individual visitors. To view Google Analytics Privacy Policy, click here: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/
This Site is not intended for use by minors. The Center for Reproductive Medicine does not knowingly allow anyone under the age of 14 to participate in any activity on the Site. The Center for Reproductive Medicine does not provide services outside of the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, by submitting information to The Center for Reproductive Medicine you are consenting to the transfer of your data to the United States and our processing of your data in the United States in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
The Center for Reproductive Medicine is an affiliate of IntegraMed America, Inc. (“IntegraMed”) Information collected from and through the Site may be provided to IntegraMed for use consistent with this Privacy Policy and applicable law. The Center for Reproductive Medicine and IntegraMed do not contract with any companies for ad serving to our site visitors.  For more info on site privacy and analytics, please click here: http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/
If you fill out a contact form and/or provide your telephone number online you should be contacted by a representative of The Center for Reproductive Medicine in order to provide you with the information you requested. Communications with or through the Site are not intended to and do not establish a patient-physician relationship, nor does it constitute the provision of healthcare services. A Notice of Privacy Practices pursuant to the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act of 1996 (“HIPAA”) is made available at the time any prospective or actual patient first receives services from The Center for Reproductive Medicine.
The Center for Reproductive Medicine takes reasonable steps to ensure the security of its website infrastructure and data, however, we make no guarantees or warranties concerning the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and cannot be responsible for the theft, destruction or inadvertent disclosure of personally identifiable information.
The Site may contain links to other web sites that The Center for Reproductive Medicine and/or IntegraMed does not own or control. The Center for Reproductive Medicine does not endorse the content on any third-party websites and is not responsible for the content of linked third-party sites, sites framed within the The Center for Reproductive Medicine Site, the privacy practices employed by third-party sites, or third-party advertisements, and does not make any representations regarding their content or accuracy. Your use of third-party websites is at your own risk and subject to the terms and conditions of use for such sites. The Center for Reproductive Medicine does not endorse any product advertised on the The Center for Reproductive Medicine Site.
In the course of developing The Center for Reproductive Medicine business, The Center for Reproductive Medicine may buy or sell assets. If another entity acquires IntegraMed or all or substantially all of its assets, personal-identifying information and other information collected from users of the Site may be transferred to the entity as one of the transferred assets. If any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against IntegraMed, all such information may be considered an asset of The Center for Reproductive Medicine and/or IntegraMed and as such may be sold or transferred to third parties.
Upon request we provide Site visitors with access to a description of information that we maintain about them and offer visitors the ability to have inaccuracies corrected in contact information. Site users can have this information corrected by writing to us at the below address:
IntegraMed Fertility
Two Manhattanville Road
Purchase, NY 10577-2113
Revised: May 20, 2016
share
Request an Appointment
251-438-4200
Request Online
